

#### **ABOUT ME**

I have been working in Cafe industry for last 10 years and I'm good at the most of cafe works, coffees and latte art as well. I'm kind, diligent, patient, eager to learn and happy to work wherever i'm needed. It'll be great honour if i can have opportunity to work with your team.

#### **CONTACTS**



0468 426 279



clidelee@gmail.com



501 Adelaide Street, Brisbane

#### **AVAILABILITY**

Mon	All day
Tue	All day
Wed	All day
Thu	All day
Fri	All day
Weekend	All day

### **REFERENCE**

#### Sam Pask

Motorwagen Owner 0410 305 466

### Henrique Boldrini Vargas

Caffe Cherrybeans Manager 0416 457 196

# CHANG-HA LEE

#### **KEY SKILLS**









Customer Service

Payment Handling

Basic Cocktails

Latte Art

#### **EDUCATION**

DIPLOMA of MANAGEMENT
Business Institute of Australia, SYDNEY NSW

RSA - NSW

Food Safety Training

**COVID-19 STAFF TRAINING** 

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Motorwagen

HEAD BARISTA | BRISBANE CITY QLD | Sep 2018 - Oct 2021

- Making Coffee, Basic Cocktails, Customer Service, Stock Control, Cash Handling, Cash-Up till.

#### Macho Macho Café & Bar

BARISTA | ASHGROVE QLD | Jun 2019 - Dec 2019

- Making Coffee, Cocktails, Customer Service, Cash Handling.

# Ripe

BARISTA | SOUTH BRISBANE QLD | Aug 2018 - Jan 2019

- Making Coffee, Customer Service, Cash Handling.

## Caffe Cherrybeans DFO

MANAGER | BRISBANE AIRPORT QLD | July 2017 – Aug 2018 - Making Coffee, Customer Service, Stock Control, Cash Handling, Closing of tills and store. Etc.

# Caffe Cherrybeans WODEN

MANAGER | WODEN ACT | June 2013 - June 2017

- Making Coffee, Customer Service, Training and hiring staff, Stock Control, Cash Handling, Closing of tills and store. Etc.